gomolo.com 2013-03-25

# privacy policy of gomolo.in

Your privacy is critically important to us. At RaViSa we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your income level or sexual preference for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:  
RaViSa Infomedia Private Limited (“RaViSa”) operates several websites including RaViSa.in and gomolo.in. It is RaViSa’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, RaViSa collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. RaViSa’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how RaViSa’s visitors use its website. From time to time, RaViSa may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

RaViSa also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. RaViSa does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to RaViSa’s websites choose to interact with RaViSa in ways that require RaViSa to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that RaViSa gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at gomolo.in to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with RaViSa or its contractors and affiliated Organizations are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, RaViSa collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with RaViSa. RaViSa does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

Aggregated Statistics 

RaViSa may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, RaViSa may monitor the most popular blogs on the gomolo.in site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. RaViSa may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, RaViSa does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

RaViSa discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on RaViSa’s behalf or to provide services available at RaViSa’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using RaViSa’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. RaViSa will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, RaViSa discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when RaViSa believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of RaViSa, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an RaViSa website and have supplied your email address, RaViSa may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with RaViSa and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. RaViSa takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. RaViSa uses cookies to help RaViSa identify and track visitors, their usage of RaViSa website, and their website access preferences. RaViSa visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using RaViSa’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of RaViSa’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, RaViSa may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in RaViSa’s sole discretion. RaViSa encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a gomolo.in account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

The above content is adapted from Creative Common licensing framework
